I'm going to record, I'm going to show my screen.
Oops, Sophie's coming in now. Okay,
can everyone see that okay? Yes. All right, we're all good.
So welcome everybody. Hi. Is our webcam masterclass.
So we're just going to run through all the basics, really.
So it'd be good if you're just starting out with cam or if you're wanting a bit of
a refresh or whatever, it's always good, isn't it?
To make these calls and especially the ones that, you know, give an overview of so
much stuff. So hopefully, you know, if anyone's got anything to add, then please
feel free to put your hand up or chip in and just, you know, add whatever
you can because we've all got our own experience somewhere and it helps, we can learn
from each other. Okay, so let's get started.
And do you want to talk about what we'll cover?
Yeah, sure. Okay, so what we will cover in this call, the importance of your profile,
your webcam setup, your webcam persona, how to get more clients into
your chat room, a good cam routine and helpful tips and advice.
So yeah, I feel like if we nail all this, then yeah, we're flying.
Okay, so the importance of your profile. So first thing
we'll talk about is the about you section.
So this is like the bio bit on your profile where it's got all the text.
In here, I think maybe Sami, you were gonna talk a little bit about this, about what
to write on this, yeah. I'll hand over to you then, Sami, if that's okay.
Okay, so for your profile, obviously we
send out a document already that literally gives the information of
how to change your profile picture, what you, how to do your strap line, your
summary line, how to use your profile, how to edit, like all
the steps of how to actually do it. So I've just done a little document if
anyone's interested at the end of what content to put in your profile.
I've tried to do it for as many personas as I possibly can, but obviously I can't
cover everyone. So if you, if I haven't covered it, then you can always let me know.
But I think the document we already send out gives you quite a lot of information
of how to do everything. So I've just put in a little bit about what to write
and how to write it and just explained a little bit more of like opening tabs and
what to write under each tab and just like really filling it out with as much information
and content as you can, if that makes sense.
So yeah, so if anyone, rather than going through it now and taking up everyone's
time, if anyone at the end wants to just message me, I've written a load of stuff
up today and I'm more than happy to send it over and help with writing your profile.
Thank you, Sami. Amazing, thank you, Sami.
Yeah, you write the document that we already have is a bit more, it shows the logistics
of it, but not so much what to actually write.
So yeah, this is perfect, thank you, Sami.
So yeah, on this bit, like Sami said, it's just a text that explains about you and
what you enjoy on cam or what you enjoy, you know, just in your normal life or your
normal made-up life or whatever. But yeah, I'm sure with Sami's documents as well,
you can really write something on there. Sort of like how to pack
that out and how to, once you get your persona, how to open other tabs and what to
write under each tab, you know, to section it off and to just basically make it your
unique selling point and make it the best that you can make it.
I think the important thing is when you're writing your about section, about me section,
is that you're writing to your ideal client.
So obviously when you're first starting out, you might not know what that is.
So it's okay to keep it a bit vague, but you know, once you get going, you'll kind
of figure out what type of guys are coming in your chat room the most and spending
the most and what they like from you. Do they like that you're the shy girl next
door or do they like. That you say you do a certain job or do they like a certain
thing about your appearance or whatever so I always say to my girls like just
you know once you've been on a few times you'll get an idea of what most of your
clients are liking about you and then you know what to put on your about you section
what to focus on you know whether I remember ages ago well you said about visualising
what you want from your clients so like what you know sit and think about and
visualise it and manifest it a little bit of what you want from them and then incorporate
that into your profile and I think that that can really work as well yeah yeah definitely
because I've done this a few times obviously your profile you know can change as
you change and you know mine's changed a few times over the years but like recently
I thought I I want to get more submissive clients so like what do they what do they
want from me what am I not what's not coming across in my profile that might come
across better so I thought about that and I just changed not even much of the wording
I most of the wording and content was the same it was the way it was written it was
the way I was speaking to them so I was speaking to them in dominant way so yeah
there's a lot to think about there isn't there in that about you section
um but I think for new starters you know because there
are a lot of agencies out there that will just write that about you section for a
person and it will have nothing that makes you any different from any other girl
so I would say think about what's unique about you what's fun about you
and flirty and not even doesn't even have to be something sexual does it and just
think about what hobbies you have or what things you like what you can do what you
like to talk about and put some personal stuff in there because I think that gives
clients more of an opportunity to get to know you and to become regulars rather than
just you know coming for a quick play because you look nice yeah
exactly and you know the clients have actually picked up on that that some agencies
do just write a generic in like they'd probably just do a copy and paste for every
girl maybe change the odd word here or there because some of my regular clients
have actually said to me I like how your profile is just like no authentic to you
and I've seen some girls they've all just got the same stuff written and I'm like
yeah exactly because the group manager would have just copied and pasted that in
so the clients actually noticed that too so so yeah I think we'll stay away from
that one just like we said make it more personable okay so moving on to the next
one um so pictures so the pictures on your profile and first
of all discuss the profile pictures so you're allowed to have free and I'd recommend
having all three to be honest um like you know having one uploaded for each one and
for your one obviously you want to pick the one that you feel like is most eye-catching
and you can ask us as well if you're if you've got a couple of pictures that you're
you know you're talking with what one to pick for the first picture just ask your
mentor or asking the group or ask any of us and we'll all we've all been more
than happy to give you some advice um you want to make sure your profile pictures
are you're taking up quite a lot of the photo you're not too far back because then
when you're a small little photo on the big screen you're not going to be able to
see you as properly so and see you as well sorry so if there's all bits around the
profile I don't need to be there around the profile picture you can crop that out
and you can also upload pictures to a free gallery and your private gallery so free
gallery obviously the clients can see these for free and the private gallery they
have to pay to see these pictures so just bear that in mind when choosing what to
put in what so I put them all in like tame photos in the free gallery and if you've
got any more revealing photos or you know just any different kinds of photos like
for example pictures of your feet or stuff like that you can put these in the private
gallery because they'll definitely sell and you can write captions for the private
gallery photos which we recommend to do because you can write on the caption I don't
know how does my bum look or you know fully naked or whatever it is whatever it is
that you are in that shot or what you're doing or whatever write a little tease
as to what the shot is so then they see that and think oh I want to see that I want
to see how it feet look or whatever else and then they'll pay to see it um yeah
I think that's it for the pictures it's just the free gallery the private gallery
and the profile pictures um if I'm not mistaken um there's actually something else
that you can do and I've not done this yet um I think was it ukc that told us about
this you can make different galleries for different clients so you can actually
upload you know, a gallery and put pictures in
and it might have a little code or something like that, and you can share that with
certain clients and only like certain clients will then buy that gallery.
So for example, I have clients that I do domination on, then I also have clients
that I do like the girlfriend experience on, so the pictures that each of them seen
would be actually quite different. So this would be good if you have different personas
that you play, you can direct your domination clients, for example, to your domination
pictures and then girlfriend experience clients to your girlfriend experience pictures.
So yeah, I think this is another good little feature that you've got on the website.
How do we do this? I've just seen the message in the chat.
What we will do actually, we will make a video on how to do this and put it onto
one of the courses and also send it in the chat once it's done.
I think that'll probably be the best way to do it.
Okay, is there anyone else want to say anything about the pictures?
Yeah, with pictures consent. So whenever you upload pictures, whether
it's profile pictures, free gallery, whatever, you always need to give consent for
your pictures. So it will pop up, it does pop up.
Does it pop up? Doesn't it? When you add pictures, does it pop up organically, I
think, and ask if you're the only person in the picture?
It doesn't, it doesn't pop up, you then have to click on your consent under,
I think, edit profile. And then it will pop up as in like, I uploaded nine pictures
today into my gallery. So then I had to click on gallery because nine pictures didn't
have consent and then click consent. Yeah.
And something that's really also important, though, is if you're going to change
your profile picture at night or at the weekend, it, your
consent won't be, it won't upload until someone's reviewed it from AdultWork.
And they don't work, I think after like five o'clock during the week, and they don't
like weekends at all. So if you're going to change your profile pictures, do it
between like nine and five, Monday to Friday.
Because if you change it like on a Saturday, like afternoon before you're going to
start work, then you're gonna have no profile picture till Monday morning.
Yeah, or between nine and three even really, because it takes them some time to moderate
it sometimes and you don't want to be there.
Yeah, unfortunately, Bernie sort of do off hours.
I think if you click on edit profile, and then you'll see the consent bit and
it's, yeah, you just click on the pictures that have got consent and say confirm.
Yeah, thank you, Sam, for that. That's okay.
Okay, so somebody's just asked in the chat, can they pay any kinds of money for the
private pictures or do you set a limit? You do actually set how much, how much you're
going to sell them for, for the whole, for the whole lot.
It's not per photo, it's for the whole bunch of them.
You can set it at a certain price and also set it how long they're able to view that,
view them for, so they can view them, they could pay five credits, for example, and
be able to view them for 24 hours or maybe you can make them view them for even longer.
The more pictures you've got in there, the more you can charge.
And also, yeah, just feel whatever feels good to you as well.
Don't undersell yourself, people will buy it.
But yeah, you can ask your mentor as well about stuff like that.
Once you've got your private gallery together, you can go through it with your mentor
and see what we think is a good price if you need help with that one.
Okay, one more thing as well. Sorry, I just remembered, from pictures, just to
make sure that you don't post pictures in your gallery that you're posting elsewhere
online. I know we say this to new girls anyway when they start, but just I
would always say, or I always say to new girls, just take pictures that are purely
for AdultWork, don't post them elsewhere because obviously they can be image searched,
you can do a reverse image search and somebody could find you on another site or
somewhere else online. So I'd always say take pictures that are just for AdultWork
if you don't want to be found online elsewhere.
Yeah, definitely. Okay, so content to sell.
So you can sell quite a few different things on AdultWork, you can sell just
like items. So for example, you can sell underwear or stockings, stuff like this
is quite popular to sell. I've sold all kinds of stuff over the years, like my old
Primark bras and knickers for like, really expensive for just an old bra or whatever
else that I was getting rid of anyway. I've actually sold weird stuff and that, but
I won't go into that at the moment. And you can also sell videos as
well. So as well as having pictures on your profile that you can sell, of course,
you can upload videos and these are sold per video.
So for each video, you put an own individual price on that and with the
videos, you don't have to have anything on there too crazy and I will like to what
you think what you maybe you'd need to put on there.
You can literally sell videos of anything.
And I think the ones on my profile is just a video of me in a bikini, just show my
body. Like people have bought it. It's not the greatest video in the world but people
have bought it. But yeah, it doesn't need to be like pulling stuff or anything like
that if you don't want to. And obviously if you do, then you can do that.
But yeah, this is another way to just boost up the credits that you're making.
Yeah, anything else got anything to say on that one?
No, okay. So ratings for that one. Oh yeah, sure.
Yeah, just because my main thing at the moment
is breastfeeding. People have asked me for bras and knickers that are covered in
my mail. But when I've uploaded those items to sell, they always get taken off.
And I finally realised I finally read into it and you can't have unclean items
for sale. They've got to be clean and whatever they can't have any bodily fluids
on them. People have asked me for like my pissy knickers, my crummy knickers, my
milky knickers, and it's not allowed. So I would say, make sure, well, at least say
the items are clean. So I'm gonna upload stuff and say that it's clean and whatever,
and if random buys it, I'll send a clean pair.
But if it's a regular client and they ask me for something specific, I'll say, do
you know what I mean, buy it, and I will spray some milk onto you for it or whatever.
So just, because it took me a while to find that it has got to be clean, by the way.
Just thought I'd add that in there. Thank you.
That's the kind of clients I get. Yeah, thank you, that's
a good point. We all get those clients. Like I've had weird, like not weird, but
crazy requests of what the stuff they want to buy from me in the past.
But yeah, I didn't send that stuff. So
how do we do that? Okay, so we have a video, Elle, that it
was Elle, wasn't it? Oh, Elle, sorry. We have a video, Elle, on the website,
on the welcome course that actually shows you how to upload videos.
It shows you how to edit your whole profile and do everything that we're discussing
here. And also there's a document that Sami was talking about earlier that we have,
which tells you step-by-step how to do it as well.
So afterwards we can direct you to that. And then if you've got any questions, of
course we can help. Okay, so moving on to the next one.
Ratings and giving feedback. So having ratings on your profile is
something that you want to really look to build up over time.
So obviously you'll start off with none and that's absolutely fine because in the
beginning, you can play the new cards and stuff like that and they'll see that you're
new because they'll see what dates you started, it says on your profile, and then
they can also see you're new by not having any ratings or just having a few.
So it's fine in the beginning, obviously, when you don't have any, but over time
you wanna really try your best to get your ratings built up.
And by, sorry, to do this, one really good thing that you can do to really help build
yours up is to give ratings out or give feedback out.
So every time you have a chat with a client, well, it's not every single time, I
think the chat has to be over a certain amount of time.
I'm not actually sure how long it is, but even the chat set at a couple of minutes,
you still get asked to give feedback. So yet most of your conversations, you'll be
asked to give feedback on the clients. If you remember something about them in the
session, maybe you can write it down or something like this.
You can write that on your feedback form for them.
So for example, if you were discussing dogs or whatever else, you could say, oh,
I can't wait to come back and we can chat about what your new favourite dog breed
is or whatever it is. I mean, I don't know, whatever that like, whatever it is, you
can write something like that, that's personable to them.
And they're like, oh yeah, she remembers.
And then they'll see it. Maybe they'll leave you a rating as well, which is what
we want. And then also they'll come back, hopefully.
So giving our feedback to the clients is basically just as important, I'd say, as
trying to build your own up because they both go hand in hand.
And you can also just give out generic feedback too because sometimes I'll have so
many chats and I'd be like, oh, I don't remember who I said.
So I just say, had so much fun with you, can't wait till next time or whatever it
else. And although it is just a generic one, at least I've just done it then, you
know, and it gets your name out there on more profiles.
So yes, that's what I'd like to say on that one.
Has anyone else got anything to add on this one?
Something that I've been doing recently, cause I never used to ask for feedback.
Some girls do, some girls, you know, say, you know, it would be really nice if you
left me some feedback, which I think is fine.
But I never used to do that really. But I always got a lot of feedback.
I think it's because I make each guy feel like they're special.
Like I'm like, oh, you know, you're not like the others.
I really like talking to you kind of thing.
And then they want to leave feedback. But recently, because I've been doing a bit
more doming, I have made guys come in and out of my chat like three or four
times. So it looks like we're having separate chats and then make them leave feedback
for each chat. So it's just like, my feedback's massive now.
And that's just a way of bumping it up. If you've got guys who are like quite sub,
then you can get them to just come out and in again so that they can leave a feedback
for every time they're chatting to you. That was a good little tip.
Yeah, that's a good little tactic. The girls have just said that it's actually four
minutes. So if you're in a chat with someone for four minutes, then you'll get the
option to leave them feedback. Yeah, I've always asked my clients for feedback because
I have always done the domination stuff and you said that you don't ask.
So then I also tried that as well. I tried both things.
So it's up to you, you can try both. But I think it depends more on what type of
persona you are, whether you would ask or not.
But yeah, you can always ask as well if you feel like that fits with your persona.
And I've always asked to be honest. But it also works if you don't, because obviously
you built up loads before you asked, didn't you?
Okay, there's something in the chat. Let me just, yeah, set them a task.
Yeah, that's perfect. Like you just, I say, this is a task I've set you to go and
leave me four feedbacks or whatever else and tell everyone how amazing I am.
Okay. So if you're gonna chat about this next one, are you?
The direct IM, SMS and phone calls? Yes. Great,
thank you. I thank you, that's fine. No worries.
Okay, so there was actually a call on the website on this, but then I've just found
out it got deleted unfortunately through none of any one of the ECTs fault.
So I'm gonna try and remember as much as I can about what I said.
I'm very sweet surprised with small baby.
So bear with me. And if anyone wants to jump in and help, that would be fabulous.
And so to set up phone calls, it's a lot more straightforward than the
SMS. So I believe you go to your registration details
first and tick the services that you would like.
And so I've literally got every service ticked except escort
services. And so I don't wanna do meets. So I've got webcam work, phone chat, SMS
chat, content create and alternative. So if you click your phone
chat, I don't think you exactly have to verify your phone number.
We will double check this for you and let you know.
We just tick that and then add your mobile number in the phone
chat. Once you've ticked that box on registration services, you then go to my
details, edit profile, and then there should be a new tab on your
profile saying phone chat. Then you go onto that.
Always click unless you want them to, no, unless you wanna
call them. So pre-booked phone chat is when you call them.
So I have that to say to call them. I find it like, I just find
it a bit stressful because you get a text and then you've got sort of a 10 minute
window to ring them, I think. Whereas if
they ring you, once you've set your availability just to available, they can just
ring you. So your phone just rings normally and you just answer it.
And it's an obvious number. It's an 0208 number I think.
And it says to accept this call from AdultWork, press one.
So you always press one and then there's the client on the end of the phone.
And so you put your number in, set your rate.
I've currently got my price. At two credits a minute but I tend to get more calls
at one credit a minute um and I mean they're cheapskates but you really
don't have to do a lot like I'll be like cleaning the house or cooking or whatever
you can just do anything and just take a phone call basically um and you can mess
around with the price to see what's best for you um so that's that one um
they don't get your number do they so if you do it that way
they don't get your number no on your profile so
I'm just going on my profile my contact tab so the phone chat direct chat
so it says on my profile if someone wanted to ring me they ring 0203-455-0150
and then they enter their user ID which is like a six digit number I think six
or seven digit number so they enter their user ID um and
then I'm sure they enter my user ID as well but whatever that's up to the client
to sort um you can you know tell them stuff over email but just say
I'll go on my profile go on my contact page and ring that 0203 number to get through
to me um and then I think that's it phone chat and
then on the SMS chat you have to verify your
phone number so if you're on the main I'm
just double checking you go up to I think it's on my details
and anyone remember where it is the SMS it's
my details registration the mobile verification yeah so my details
then registration and then mobile activation it's at the top of the page centre
yes perfect thank you yeah top left underneath
where it says registration and regional details mobile phone activation and SMS alerts
so you have to be um verified for SMS alerts to get SMS
messages from clients so click on go there and then I mean my pops up and says verified
but it does it comes up and says basically says do this and do that
and they will text you with a code it's usually two letters and then a few numbers
and you have to text that back but and we have to stress this through no fault of
the ECCs a lot of girls it's not it's just not working for them um we
don't know if it's and also on on this when it says to verify number you select which
network you're with but obviously there's a million networks out there and there's
only like six in the list or something the big obvious ones like o2 um ee whatever
but your network if it's a smaller network for example gif gaf or live
live like a mobile or stuff like that yours is a smaller network it will be under
one of the big networks for example I think if graph uses O2 I think like
I might mean might use three to find that out select that on the drop down menu when
you verify your mobile number um and then they'll send you a text and hopefully you
will be able to send that text back and you might need to speak to your network provider
and get them to put premium texts on um you know if
you've ever text like the radio or a competition or something when it's just a little
five digit number um you have to might have to put that on or you
might need credit if you've just got minutes and text messages as part of your contract
plan it may not let you do that because it's like well that's a premium number that's
not included in your normal texting plan so you might need to add credit or just
speak to your network provider basically and hopefully that will work for you so
once that's verified you can then go on registration details um
and where are we registration details and your selector services
so then you can check the mess um it's um
it's very sporadic the texts you can't
set the price for them and the client will text you and I think the first initial
one costs them one credit, then if you send a reply, you
get half a credit in payment. So that's like what, 25, 30 pay.
And then they'll text you and then you pay each for your replies.
So if they text you, don't be thinking, oh, sounds made 20p there.
You don't, you only make money off your advice.
So always reply to them. Don't send them essays, send them a few words.
And I often send like, oh, and then I did this, dot, dot, dot.
So then they'll text back like, oh, and what else?
And then you're like, oh, and then this, dot, dot, dot.
You know, just keep it going because it is a small amount of money, but you can text
someone all day and you know, have 10 credits in your account and it does build up,
it is quite good, but they are very sporadic.
I've put on my profile, that's my preferred contact method rather than email or whatever,
because obviously you can't earn money off the SMS.
You can't earn any money off the emails. And whenever anyone emails me, I go, oh,
I've only just seen this, I don't get notifications from my emails.
If you send me an SMS through my profile, I'll see it straight away or send me an
SMS when you come in online and I will come and see you.
And you know, it is a little bit of extra income and it, you
know, it can build up. I think that
is it. If anyone's got anything else to add, have I missed anything?
Thank you, Sophie. I think that's it, isn't it, for those.
We did say at some point maybe- If anyone wants to message me about this.
Maybe at some point we could do another call on it.
We can all chip in and do another call on it because it'd be useful to have that
call back up anyway. Yeah, definitely
happy. Happy to do that. Did I
just get muted then? Hello? Hello, yeah, you're back.
Oh, we'll mention about the direct IM as well.
So direct IM is, it's basically, it's just, you're going
live on cam but you're not showing your video.
So it's basically just like a live chat. Kind of like the, what
was it called? Like back in the day, the thing that used to have that like messenger
that used to do is kind of reminds me of that.
The best end, that was it, yeah. Reminds me of that because it can't see you but
obviously you're just typing. So a lot of our girls actually have been using this
and I feel like because one's been doing well if it maybe it's spared the other ones
to do it because in the chat, I see often that the girls are writing in there, oh,
I just turned on direct IM while I was, you know, sat at home, not done, ready for
cam and made like, you know, like 80 credits, over a hundred credits, this and that,
just from turning it on and just sat there typing as they were doing something else.
So yeah, I think this is a good one to do if you're, you know, not in the mood to
show your face or whatever on cam, it's good to turn on and try out.
With the direct IM, I'd recommend before doing it to
lower the price a little bit of what you're charging because it basically, when you
log into direct IM. When
you log into direct IM, it's just the same as logging into webcam.
So your usual webcam prices will come up for the direct IM chat.
So you wanna lower them a little bit because people pay more for webcam because they
can see you, of course, than they would just for the text.
So yeah, you can speak to your mentor about this and also see what the competition
is charging kind of thing, and then pick what you feel comfortable with, you know,
in a good range. You don't wanna be charging too much more than anybody else, and
you also don't wanna be undercutting yourself.
So yeah, I think that's a good one to do.
Like I said, if you don't wanna go on cam, but always just bump up your weekly credits.
Anything else to say on that one before I move on?
Actually, before we move on to cater to your market, someone mentioned emails before,
and this probably would have been something to put on this slide, but I forgot to
put it on here. So I'll talk about it now.
So you get emails from your clients and they don't come to an email, you know, like
a Hotmail or Gmail or anything like that.
They come to your email box in your profile.
So you can access this by going to my details and emails, I think it is, but we've
got all this on a document anyway. So yeah, you can access your emails and your clients
will send you emails like telling you that you'll get all different ones, but a lot
of the time you'll get emails. Where clients will tell you a really drawn out fantasy
of what they wanna do on cam with you. And then you can reply and tell them if you
wanna do that or not. You'll get emails of people asking you to meet them as well,
even if you don't have that you meet on your profile, this is completely normal.
And then you'll also just get emails off your regular clients, just checking in with
you and seeing when you're next online. So as Sophie said, you don't get paid to
reply to emails, but I would recommend replying to them, especially when you're just
on cam waiting for calls. And you don't wanna spend too long with the emails.
You don't wanna be writing out essays because like we said, you don't get paid for
it. And you also don't wanna be sending too many emails back and forth about that
client actually coming into your chat room and paying you.
So what I do personally with my emails is if it's a new client or if it's just a
freeloader client I feel I hasn't actually came into my chat, I will always just
try and direct them into my group or private chat.
I'll just say, oh yeah, that sounds amazing.
I'd really love to do that. Or what, you know, obviously if I'm comfortable too of
course, and then say, you know, let's, let's speak about this in private or, you
know, whatever, like I'll always direct them into there because you probably will
get a lot of freeloaders in the emails as well.
So you don't wanna spend too long, but it's also, it's also good to reply to emails
because then the clients will say, see that you're online and then come in and chat
with you so yeah, that's another little thing to mention.
And finally, cater to your market. So we already spoke about this a little bit before
when we were speaking about the bio. Georgia.
Yeah, sure, yeah. Sorry, one second. Can I just say about the emails, just one second.
So I've actually got quite a lot of good clients from emails and there are so many
freeloaders out there and one tip I would just like to give anyone who's new starting
here is set some special offers on your profile and
you can message me after how to set that up or whatever and then when they email
you and say, oh, could you do a session with me on Wednesday, say at 9
p.m. , what would you like me to have? So I'll say, oh, a nappy, tin of beans,
blah, blah, that's just for example of some of the bookings at iPad because
they can't actually leave you a deposit. I say, come online quickly, do a special
offer with me. So it'd be like a two minute special offer which will be like, I don't
know, 30 credits, 40 credits, 50 credits, whatever you charge and then they've paid
that as a deposit. So obviously you then need to stick to that but it's a good way
of them leaving you a deposit and you knowing that they're a genuine client that
wants something from you at this time on this day because there are a lot of guys
that do wanna book in but they can't, you can't pre-book a cam call with a deposit
so that's a good way of like making a deposit and pre-booking a call and separating
their freeloaders from the guys that actually wanna pay you for something.
Amazing, thank you, Sammy. That's a great idea, I think.
Cool. And also, I'd say, just to be aware,
and be aware that there's lots of places that you can go, so there's people that
will be like, you know, I'm looking for a sugar baby.
You know, I wanna give you a thousand pound a month for this or that or whatever,
but they're just messaging everybody. So you can, if you're not sure about that,
you can message in the WhatsApp group and just ask us and we'll usually, loads of
other people would have had the same message or we've had it before or whatever.
So just be wary, always be cautious. If you get emailed something, always be suspicious
of it. You know, just view them through that lens before you do anything and don't
do anything without getting paid for it first because, you know, in the past girls
have, you know, done stuff or like replied to stuff or whatever
it is, do not do anything without getting paid for it first because...
And look at their feedback. Always look if they've got feedback.
So a couple of times I've been, I've got emails, if they've got zero feedback, I'm
like, I don't even bother replying. If I can see like 100 feedback or 200 or 250,
I'm like, oh, okay, you know, I'll take this one.
I'm gonna go with this. So yeah, look at their feedback because that definitely tells
you something about your client. Yeah, definitely.
And it's keeping a little number, it's not going to go.
So, easy to see. Yeah, and one final thing on the emails
that reminds me, you do get emails as well, let's say, your content has been leaked,
click here and be sent the same email to everybody and it's probably going to be
a virus or something like that. So once again, just if you get emails like that,
always just ask us, just say, screenshot it and say what you think about this and,
and we can tell you we've always seen that email over the past week 100 times like
they've just been sending it to everybody.
So, so yeah, there's just stuff like that as well on there sometimes, like little
scums. So yeah, just be aware. Okay, so cater to your market,
we've already kind of spoke about this one.
So do you think we should move on to the next slide?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay,
so your webcam setup. So it's really important to make
sure that your webcam setup is okay. You know, the clients are going to click into
you and if they can't see you clearly or whatever, you know, it's not appealing to
them when they click into your room, they're just going to click out.
So, you know, this is the first thing that's most important really because we're
trying to get them to stay there for as long as possible.
And it doesn't even give us a chance for them to get to know us or talk to us or
whatever if they if they can't see us properly.
So, yeah, making sure you've got a decent webcam and mic, that
the quality on them is okay. I mean, with most laptops these days, you've got a HD
webcam, haven't you? But you can always buy like Logitech ones
or whatever you can buy plugin webcams that you can just click on to whatever you're
using. But just yeah, making sure that the quality is good.
HD webcam, if possible, I think they're always better.
Lighting, so as you can see on the picture, she's got a ring light, so that same
as the one I've got in front of me right now.
You can get these on Amazon or, you know, even Argos, you know, wherever
there's loads of different ones you can get.
You can get ones that have like clickers, like remotes so that you can turn them
up and down. Usually they have a little holder, like you can see she's got a phone,
I think, or you can, there's a little holder for your phone so you can take content
as well for cam. If you haven't got one yet, I think I would always recommend
buying a ring light. But if you haven't got one yet, then just making sure that the
light is coming from behind your screen. So it's lighting you from that direction,
rather than it coming down from the ceiling or being from behind you and then you're
going to be silhouetted. So just making sure the light is behind you.
Before I had one, like in the early days, I just used to put a big bright lamp behind
my screen so that would light me up properly.
And I know, Georgie, you sometimes use like LED lights and stuff, don't you?
Yeah, so especially if I'm camming, like, of an evening or something like
that when it's darker anyway, I'll still have the ring light on me in front of me
so they can clearly see me. But then in the background, maybe I'll have the lights
switched off in the house so the lighting's lower, but they can still see me but
there's a darkness as well. And then in the background, maybe I'll set up some LED
lights so like a pink light or a red light or whatever it is, and it just adds like
a different dimension to the shot. It actually looks quite good, I think, and that's
something you can play around with. You can get LED lights really cheap like, you
know, a couple of quid or whatever else online.
And yeah, I think it just adds something more to it as well, especially if you're
coming over night time so that's something to consider too.
Yeah, I think when the room's dark, and you've got like a bright ring light, like
pointing towards your face, it does help to have like a duller light behind you,
whether that's like LED or like if I'm in my bedroom I have my lamp on because it's
quite dull. But otherwise it can wash you out, can't it?
The light can make you just look really white.
Exactly. It's good to have something behind you sometimes.
Thinking about the space around you, so, you know, depending on how I'm feeling
or what persona I'm playing or whatever, I might have like items around me that are
enticing. I will try and fill up like at least this much of the screen that
I'm filling up right now, so I'll try not to be like really far away, although of
course you can move in and out. But depends on your setting, doesn't it?
I mean, I've seen some of the girls settings are really nice with like fairy lights
or like nice lights and they've got the bed and the canopy and stuff.
And some of yours looks really nice, always looks nice.
So, yeah, just think about the space around you.
Does it reflect? You know skipping ahead there's the point at the end but does it
reflect your persona does it reflect who you are you know if you're the girl next
door it's okay for you to look like you're just you know you're just in bed or on
the sofa or whatever um but perhaps if you're you know if you're being dominant perhaps
you want to have some like some equipment around you or you want to have you know
your space want you don't want to be in a little you know a little bedroom and be
dominant you want to you want your space to reflect the person that you're that you're
trying to be on cam um comfort yeah I like it
was uh Georgia that put that on there I like that you put that on there Georgia I
suppose it's important for you to feel comfortable because you want to be inviting
and you want to have good energy you know and you don't want to be sat somewhere
where you're uncomfortable um or they're saying that I do
get quite uncomfortable when I'm on cam because I can't do it here because I think
uh it reverses the screen when you use Zoom so I don't look the same here that I
look on cam but I know when I'm on cam I have my head tilted to a certain angle and
then just know that I look best at that angle so I do get naked after a while but
um yeah I think just knowing how you look and feeling comfortable and
just like moving your body you know knowing how your body looks on cam like I know
that at certain angles like got a really good side boob or like whatever it is like
getting to know your body and how it looks on cam you know look at yourself check
in yourself and see what they're seeing and how you can you know incorporate a bit
of teas or whatever into the image that you're projecting um and
I guess when you're thinking about comfort I mean that makes me think about like
I'll have a herbal tea on the other side of my laptop and like I might have my slippers
on or something or a blanket so yeah as long as what they're seeing in their image
of the screen looks good like it doesn't matter what's around the edges um changing
it up so yeah camming in different settings I mean you can come from your phone now
I know that Georgia has done really well in the past haven't you when you've been
like in the back of the car and you've been on a long journey or something um I've
seen people do it in trains like in beer gardens um I think clients love it when
you change it up especially if you're out and about and you can come out and about
um I think it's just exciting for them to see you in a different scenario isn't it
um yeah is there any is there anything else you'd add ladies to that I think
you covered it yeah that's about it for webcam setup okay so
we're onto persona okay so your webcam persona when
choosing your webcam persona we play for with it and try not to get too caught up
in what you think the client might like instead think about what character you would
like to play and go from there it could be the innocent girl next door the naughty
nurse the bored and horny housewife the obedient sub the MILF the dominatrix
the list goes on there's so many more than that as well and alternatively you
could just be completely yourself and show your clients the real you do whatever
you're comfortable with and if you're not sure yet what you're comfortable with you
can experiment with playing different personas to see what feels best for you experiment
with makeup clothes setting and more so yeah so of course in the beginning um
you know you're likely not to know what you want to what you want to do or who you
want to be on there and that's totally fine um it's just like a fun time really to
just you know play about and see what works for you and um also if you're not even
sure about what the different personas are for example you can ask us or you can
just take a look on the website at the girls who were online and then you'll start
to see you know what different what different roles that are to play and who
you play on webcam could be completely different to who you are in real life as well
and that also is a little bit fun too to try something new and so yeah so over the
over time you will start to you will obviously find what works for you and then and
build on it and become more comfortable in that persona and then maybe think oh I'd
like to try something else as well because I basically do quite a lot of different
things and it works for me and I do and I gauge it off what clients come into
my room of how to what type of person I'm going to be with them so for example if
they come in and say hi goddess behind me or, you know, something like that, then
I know straight away that this client is a sub and I need to be a Dom.
Or if I have a client that comes in that just wants to be flirty and stuff like that,
maybe they just want like a little bit of a flirty chat, like the girlfriends kind
of thing. So yeah, you can play different personas with different clients too.
And yeah, I think it's good to just not put so much pressure on, you know, having
it all figured out in the beginning, like, oh, I'm the sub, so now I need to know
everything about being a sub. Because even if, you know, you don't know everything
and I mean, you're not gonna know everything of course, but even if you feel like
you don't know much, you will learn about it as like in your sessions.
And it's okay as well, if the sessions don't go how you want it to go, or
like, you know, they don't go as successfully as you would like them to, especially
in the beginning. So for example, I've had girls say to me, oh, you know, it was
going so well and then I said something and he mustn't have liked it and then he
left. He could have left for any reason. First of all, there could have been anything.
And secondly, that's okay because, you know, and then you'll realise, okay, so maybe
next time I'll try saying something different or this or that and you'll build, you
know, your persona and you'll build the type of phrases and stuff you'll say.
And of course it does change with clients as well, so which makes it a little bit
more complicated, but the more you do it, the more you will know what clients want
to hear what and yeah. Okay. Is there anything?
Can I just say something? Also, no matter what
persona you've got, obviously mine's quite like a set persona and quite unique.
Even now I still get guys that come in and be like, oh, they're not into taboo, they're
not into being like dominated or anything like that.
They're just like, oh, can I see your tits or whatever, you know, like, they just
want a bit of fun. And sometimes that's really fun as well.
Like, I don't know, like sometimes I'm like, yeah, okay then, like, you know, like
I just have fun with it in the moment. I don't always, I do have my set persona obviously
and my set sort of profile and everything else, but I think no matter what you have,
you're still always gonna have guys that come in and maybe they've not even read
it or maybe they've just a chance or whatever.
And that can also be really good fun and you can be playful with it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Sometimes you don't want to and you might be like, no, sorry,
this is not what I want, but I quite enjoy it sometimes.
It's fun to like just have something different and be a bit playful and enjoy, actually
enjoy what you're doing and have fun with it too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's cool. I was gonna say a similar thing.
I was gonna say, yeah, just don't, I know we're talking a lot about the persona here,
but don't feel trapped in your persona. Like some of the best calls will come from
just being open and a bit silly and, you know, like having fun.
And then sometimes like someone comes with something and I'm like, oh, that's weird.
I don't know anything about that. It's a bit odd.
And then actually ends up being the best call.
You just have so much fun and you're just learning stuff and like you can bounce
off each other. So yeah, I think some girls, especially in the beginning, feel
like they need to know it all. It's like, okay, I've got this client.
So what do I need to say? How does it work with this client?
But every client is different. Every client is different.
And if you get in your head that you know how clients work, like, oh, I know how
this client works, then you're probably not going to be open to having those really
nice calls because guys, they just want to be listened to.
And a lot of the time, they just want you to reflect back what they're saying to
you and what they like. You know, it's really easy when you stay open and you just
give them back what they're giving to you.
You know, they actually really like that and makes them stay for quite a while.
Yeah, definitely. I was just going to say this.
Like, I think putting aside everything, I think the main thing is what does the client
like? What does the client want? And do I feel like I want to deliver that to them?
And if I do, you know, yeah. So that's all it is really.
So if a client comes in, that's obviously a sub or whatever else, I'll know, oh,
I'll go down this route. Or if a client comes in that wants this kind of thing, I'll
go down this route. But the focus is what does the client want and how do I want
to deliver that to them? And obviously the longer you do this, you will start to
see what certain things the clients say, you know, what type of client they are.
And you'll start to see the clients that you don't want to deliver to as well.
So for example. The ones that come in and after two seconds say show me this or do
this and maybe after like a second in your private chat you don't want to do that.
But yeah it is it is good to just stay open and yeah just be playful with it like
you said. But yes I think we'll move on to the next one if there's nothing else to
say on this. No? Okay great. Yeah so how to get more clients in
your chat room. So obviously this is really important because you want the clients
to be there especially when you first start you want to get as many in as possible.
So try bidding to be on the front page that can really help you to be seen.
So we there is a video on how to do this on the welcome course isn't there and I
think that you know we have a separate video anyway that we send to you so this is
something that your mentor will help you with when you first start out.
But yeah you basically bid credits so you pay credits to be
on the front page of the website and the more you pay the further up you're going
to be in the search so you know you're going to be the first few girls if you bid
more than anybody else. It will cost you something between like one and maximum
six or seven I would say credits and don't usually spend more than about four credits
really and you bid per hour so you bid credits to be on the
front page for that hour. So Georgia is a lot better than me which I realised recently
when we came together at setting an alarm on her phone so she sets an alarm for like
five to the hour so that she can bid for the next hour so she knows she's always
on the front page that's a really good thing to do.
Yeah you know what I do this every time even after like eight years I still do it
and because I'll just forget because if I don't do it then I'll think oh fuck it's
like one minute past nine and I forgot to do it and then I'm out then for the whole
hour so yeah I just set alarms because honestly girls it's just you think you'll
remember but sometimes you won't and then you'll kick yourself that you didn't set
the alarm. Yeah which I do all the time. Or alternatively
or you can do both you don't have to do one or the other but most people do one
or the other so alternatively you can try free chat so there's a box that you can
tick in the if you go to edit profile and webcams the webcam tab and then webcam
settings and there's a box that you can take to say that I'll provide free chat so
then guys can come in and out of your chat room for free and can chat to you for
a little bit it's supposed to be so you can entice them into a group or a private
chat with you. If you're putting your free chat on it asks you how
long you'd like to allow the guys to come in your free chat for and how regularly
so I think what I always set it to is what's the normal thing to set
it to like? I just set it to five minutes to be honest but you can do for maybe 10
15 or something like that but I personally don't want them in there more than five
minutes if they're not paying. Yeah five minutes takes 24 hours.
Yeah you can set them in five minutes over 24 hour periods or whatever you feel but
yeah you don't want them in there much longer because free chat can be can be like
so many freeloaders in there so a little way the freeloaders just set it at five
minutes if they come in they like the look of you they'll take you into and they
like how the conversations go and they'll take you into a paid chat you don't want
to spend longer in there with them and just be giving your time away for free because
we're not here to sit and chat for free. Personally I don't really do free chat very
rarely because I just don't feel like it keeps me in a good mindset I don't feel
like it keeps me in a good space and I'd rather be watching tv and waiting for a
call to come in and then give all my attention to that one person.
I do see a lot of new sometimes new girls like feel like they have to be on free
chat all the time and then they get quite burnt out and overwhelmed and just like
into a negative mindset and then you're just manifesting negativity for yourself
so I think only do it you know if you feel comfortable with being
in a chat room with loads of people who're trying to get your attention and I
think the people that do it and make it work for them maybe go on and do it for
like 10 or 15 minutes just to get themselves seen and chat to a few people and then
have a break from it and then maybe go on it you know an hour or so later or whatever
for 10 minutes so yeah try not to get burnt out with it but it can be a really good
way to entice clients in. Get them to want to talk to you.
Also with free chat now, they're never used to have it, but you can actually see
who's got credits and who hasn't, can't you?
So you can see next to their username whether they've got credits or not.
So don't bother spending any time on people who don't have any credits.
Email old regular clients when returning back to cam after time off.
So anytime that you go on cam, really, it's a good idea to click on your messages
and the top tab when you've logged in, click on messages, and then it will bring
up any messages that you've got. So just reply, a quick reply, like G said, I don't
spend time sending long replies to people, but I say, yeah, that sounds great, come
and speak to me on cam about it. Pretty much that's all I say.
But you can also go through your old messages and see clients that you've spoken
to before that you've, maybe old regulars or whatever, and send them a little message
and say, I'll be online tonight, or I'm online at the moment, love to see you, just
give you something to do while you're waiting for calls.
And that brings guys in sometimes. And also on that, you know,
with regular clients, you can be put on someone's hot list.
So that, you know, obviously, we've been doing it for years now.
So I've got lots of regulars that I've spoken to for years, but because I am on their
hot list, when I log in, even if I haven't logged in for a while, I know that they
come straight to see me, and I know that's because, you know, they get a notification
that I've logged in because I'm on their hot list.
So if you're really enjoying chatting to someone and you'd like them to come back
or whatever, just ask them to put you on their hot list so that they'll know next
time you're going to be online. Set special offers for specific
clients. That's what Sammy was talking about before, I guess, that you can set, yeah,
you can set offers depending on the needs of each client.
Make a social media for your campus owners to direct clients to your AdultWork.
Yeah. So yeah, a lot of people have Instagram or Twitter is a good one.
I think you can link your Twitter, can't you?
So you can put your AdultWork link on your Twitter to say that you're online.
I think it's only Twitter that you can link, isn't it?
To your AdultWork profile. Yeah. Yeah. But any way that you can get seen,
there is like a little banner thing that you can copy from AdultWork that you can
put on other sites. But yeah, anything that you can do to drum up some attention,
I suppose, or to get your name out there is a good thing.
Did you say anything else on that, G? That's more your area than mine.
Yeah. So obviously with the social media, you think, I might echo that
by the way. It's all right. Yeah. I think it makes it echo, doesn't it?
With the social media, you don't have to, you don't have to do that, of course, but
that's just something that you can do and something that some of our girls do.
So for example, they'll have an Instagram or a Twitter called whatever their cam
name is. So like goddess Ruby, for example, what mine is.
And then on there, they'll put like pictures on of them getting ready for cam or
like when they're ready and stuff like that.
Just got ready, I'll be on cam like live from like 9 PM or whatever else.
They come chat to me and then they'll put the AdultWork link.
So I think it can be a good way definitely to get clients in because then they're
not just following you on your profile on AdultWork, they're also following your
Instagram or your Twitter. So then they get to see pictures of you and little updates,
and then they might get more excited then to come into your chat room.
But with that being said, I wouldn't reply to them on social media because then they're
thinking, oh yeah, I'll just speak to it on social media then, I don't need to pay.
So I would just use that just to put yourself out there and direct people in, but
I wouldn't actually chat to them on there because then they're going to think they
can just talk to you for free. What you can actually do is on your Instagram and
maybe you can do it on Twitter too. I've just had one set up on mine and I cringe
at myself a little bit, but it's good because it works.
You can set up an auto reply. So whoever messages
you on your Instagram and maybe Twitter too, whatever they say, they'll just send
a reply and they'll say, hey, blah, blah, like their username.
And then you can write whatever you want on there.
So you could say, I don't reply to messages on here.
If you would like to speak to me, you can speak to me via my AdultWork.
You can email me on there or come to a private chat or whatever it is.
You can write a short little message, little flirty message to try and get them into
your chat because then they'll know, oh, actually there's no point in me.
Messaged her on here because she's not going to reply.
So that's something else you can do on your social media if you have one for your
AdultWork. What am
I doing? I'm zooming in on you. Okay,
shall I talk about this a little bit because I just added this on to the end, didn't
I? So I thought that it was good to just briefly mention that
it's good to have a cam routine. So if you have like a list of things that you know
are in your awareness, like a checklist that you've done before you go on cam, I
think it's just a really good idea. Like with any business, with anything that you
want to do well at, it's really good to stay intentional and conscious about what
you're doing. So these are the five things I guess that I'd always think about
when I'm going to log on. So I think about firstly my energy, which is the most important
thing because if we want to manifest clients then we have to be, you know, in a good
vibration, you have to be in a good space.
You know, whatever your feeling is going to, you know, reflect, is going to show,
is going to, you know, you're going to communicate that to your clients.
So getting in a good space, a good energetic space, putting a bit of music on, you
know, making yourself feel sexy or whatever, wearing something that you like.
Even like some candles and stuff, I do that sometimes, or like putting some massage
oil on or whatever, to get a good energetic space.
And then thinking about the space, like we said before, like I will like prep, I'll
get my lighting ready, like get myself a little blanket or whatever, you know, get
my, if I'm going to watch something or listen to a podcast or whatever, I'll set
that up. So I've sorted my space out. Then thinking about my look, so yeah, if
there's any like accessories I'm going to wear or like what kind of mood I'm in,
like what do I want to do today? So I might like put something a bit more dom on
if I'm feeling like a bit domed that day, or if I'm feeling playful, I might like
dress up or something or whatever. So I think about the look.
And then I think about the story. So I think not everyone does this, but with my
particular style of camming, I do a lot of like fantasy.
So I try and draw people in with a story.
And I think this helps, especially if you're new and you're feeling a bit nervous,
just to have, if not a story, just a little anecdote, a little something about your
day. I say this all the time, but I just think it really helps you to feel like you're,
you've got a conversation starter and you've got something to get someone interested
in you. Like my postman's just been, and he's really fit.
I've got this fancy about him or my boyfriend bought this thing, this thing for me
today. And you know, I'm just trying it on.
What do you think? You know, whatever, you can take your inspiration from the TV
or gossip or things you've heard, but I always like to have just a little tip there,
a little story to reflect how I'm feeling, what I want to talk about, but this makes
me feel a bit fun and flirty. And if I'm like a bit like stuck and someone comes
in and it's not, it's a bit like, you know, you get some people and it's just hard
to talk to them, then you've got something to say.
So I think about the story. And then last lastly, I think about it as a business.
So all the things that we said, like, you know, have I bid?
Am I going to be on the front page? Am I going to go on free chat?
Maybe I'm going to change my strap line or I'm going to add a picture.
So I'll come up more in the searches, whatever it is, you know, I think about the
business side of it, you know, like I'm promoting myself here.
I'm here to earn money. So, you know, all the little bits that I can do to treat
it like a business. Yeah. So that was that for a cam routine.
Did anyone want to add anything to that? I think that's
great. I don't think anything needs to be added to that.
But what I will say, we haven't, we've mentioned the strap line a few times, but
we haven't went into detail about what it is.
So I'll just briefly let you all know what that is.
So the strap line, basically when you're on CAM and you go on the online now section
and look at all the girls that are currently online, you're just a small little square
on a screen with other people on there. But then you have the little square with
your picture and then your username. And if they scroll over you with their mouse
or whatever else, your strap line will pop up.
So your strap line is basically just a small line, like a little sentence or two.
So that, yeah, just like a little summary of you or how you'll feel on
that day or what you're wearing. And it's just something the client will see initially.
They won't see all the stuff you've written on your bio and on your profile, unless
they click into you. So the first thing they'll see is your profile picture, your
username, your strap line. And then if you've got feedback and also they'll see your
special offers so they can see them all straight away.
And so, yeah, so with the strap line, you can change this.
And it's probably best to change it every time you go online, I'd say, even if you're
just changing, you know, a word or two in there, just because it does help if you're
coming up in searches but also you can change it to what you're feeling like each
day. So if you're feeling obviously in a certain mood that day, you can reflect that
in your strap line or if you're wearing something that you feel really amazing in
or like a new outfit or something like that, you can say, we're in my brand new outfit
today, like come tell me how I look or, you know, something like that.
And then they think, ooh, I wanna see what this new outfit is.
So yeah, you can do that on your strap line.
And I think that's actually quite important cause like I said, it's one of the first
things the client will see and we can show you how to do this.
It's just on the edit profile section, but we've got this in the document as well,
but yeah, we can show you how to do this if you can't find how to do it, but yeah.
And can I just say as well, I also wrote about how important that is today.
I forgot to say earlier. I think it's quite an important thing, the strap line, isn't
it? Like you were just saying, well, I'm like, you can literally write anything.
Like I wrote mine this morning. No, the window cleaner has just been and we had some
fun together. Like, do you wanna come in and I'll tell you more about how he got
me wet? You know, like you can just make up something.
I think it's quite an important thing to know how to use that tool because we forget
about it. I think as well, even if you've been camming a while, you just forget about
changing it and writing something new. And yeah, I think it's quite important to
keep that updated and have fun with it. I'm
obsessed with my window cleaner, so I had fun with that.
Yeah, thank you so much. Yeah, yeah. I think that's a really good point.
Yeah, there's been some good stuff on today.
It leaves me feeling most fated to go and earn some money on Pam.
Yeah, me too. And I think lastly, we've got a few helpful tips and
advice. So we may have gone through, we've probably gone through all these already,
but do you wanna go through them, Jay? Yeah, of course.
Okay, so make a note of your regular clients and useful information.
Your clients want a relationship with you.
So this is something that I feel is quite important if you're trying to build up
regular clients and they're the clients that are gonna be spending because yeah,
you do get the odd one here and there that you'll never see again, or well, you do
get a few like that, to be honest, but the regular ones coming back, this is what
you want. Of course you won't repeat business.
So try and remember things about them, or if you're someone that your memory's not
that great or you've got so many to remember them all, honestly, just get like a
notepad or something just for this, just for your clients.
You can go and buy a notepad for like a pound or something and just have it with
you. And then you can write in username and then just write like a few little points
about them throughout the session. And then afterwards you can go back and maybe
write a little bit about what they like, how the session went.
And then next time when they come in, because I've been caught out so many times,
like clients have said to me, they've come in and said, oh, I had such a great time
with you last week. Like, you know, like let's do more of that.
And I'm like, oh, what was that? And then I'm like, oh, tell me, like there was this
one client and I feel like they were just trying to trick me.
They knew that I didn't know because they were like, do you remember me?
And I was like, yeah, of course. And I didn't, I'll be honest.
I didn't because I had that many clients the week before and I just couldn't remember
this one. I didn't do what I'm telling you to do.
I didn't do it, so I should have done it.
And then he was like, oh, we'll just do more of what we've done last week.
And I said, oh, tell me what you enjoyed about last week.
And he said, I enjoyed everything. And he just kept giving me answers like that.
And I thought, you know, so I just ended up taking it somewhere and he was happy
with it anyway. But yeah, if I would have actually had it written down, I would have
known. And I think that it really does help because you might, you will forget, like
you'll think you remember everything, but you probably won't because there'll be
that many. So yeah, like I said today, they want a relationship with you.
So the more you remember about them, the better.
And then over time, you will actually start to just remember them because you'll
get them that often. So yeah, I think that's something really important you can do.
Do what? Online training courses and watch the training videos.
So this is really, really helpful, especially in the beginning and even throughout
as well, just to refresh your knowledge. We've got a lot on the website that will
help. And yeah, in the beginning, it might seem a bit overwhelming when you first
go onto the website, like, oh, how do I do this?
How do I navigate this? But we've got something on in our website that will help
you for everything on the website and stuff outside of Cameron as well.
So yes, to go to the training courses, you just log onto our website.
It's not AdultWork, so it's the Ethical Cam Community. co.uk.
And then you apply for the membership and then we'll accept you and then you can
access all of our training. And we have a brand new course coming as well.
Very soon, we have a sub-course coming. So yeah, we'll let you all know when that's
available. Next, you can ask the other members for advice in our WhatsApp support
groups. You'll get a diverse range of answers.
So yeah, this is a really good one because of course you've got your mentor to help
you, but then it's good to ask them in the chat as well because there's so many girls
in there who all have completely different experiences to you and come different
to you, or some might come the same or whatever else.
And we've all got something that we can share and offer with our advice.
And maybe someone will mention something that maybe you didn't think of, and then
you can take it there. So yeah, I think it's a very nice place and the girls are
all so supportive as well. They're all so lovely.
So yeah, it's nice to just meet the other members in there, but also you can ask
for advice and give advice too in there. Don't be afraid to ask the clients if
you don't understand what they've said. So I think we pushed on this earlier.
You don't have to have all the answers. Even doing the stuff, like if you're being
a sub, for example, or something like that, then it's more likely that you do ask
the questions and stuff and that plays into your persona more.
But even if you're playing a different kind of persona, like a dom or whatever, for
example, you can still ask questions because you're just human still.
You're not gonna know everything. And the clients actually like it too.
They like to know that they're like teaching you and stuff like that.
So yeah, always ask the clients and don't worry about it.
Don't think that you shouldn't do it because honestly it's totally fine too.
Another tip is to update your profile regularly to be in the top of searches.
So we've already mentioned that one. Treat this like a business.
Set working hours and write it on your profile.
So if you know for sure that you're gonna do certain hours this week, for example,
you can write on your profile Tuesday the 20th, October.
I'll be online from 7pm. To 11pm. Or whatever it is.
And you can write this in so then your clients, when they're visiting your profile,
they'll know and they'll say, oh, I know what time's the catcher.
Also when you're coming in certain times of the day and certain hours, you'll build
up regulars in their time because you'll have clients that will always go online
on a Friday night or always go online on the weekends or maybe you'll have clients
that go online while they're in work in the daytime.
So you'll get different clients, like different regular clients in different time
slots. So yeah, you can write it on your profile as well, like we said, to just
remind them when you're gonna be on. Invest in yourself and your brand.
So like we said earlier, it's good to invest in a ring light.
It's good to invest in outfits and equipment that make you feel
sexy, that make you feel good. And yeah, like this is your thing you're building
for yourself. So really invest in yourself, invest in it with the stuff that you
need. Also invest your time and energy into learning about this.
Yeah, it's like the old cliche saying, but it's really true that the more you put
into it, the more you'll get out. Like it's probably true of everything to be honest,
but it's definitely true with this one as well.
Okay, so do your research, read blogs and fantasies slash online
content. So as well as the website, of course, as well as our members area and the
website, you can also go online to other websites and read about different
blogs and stuff like that, all about webcamming.
The more knowledge you've got on this, the better, because you'll have so many different
types of clients coming into your room that all like different things.
And although you're not, of course you're not gonna know everything and you're not
expected to know everything, the more you read up on it and the more, yeah.
Educate yourself on it, then the more likely you are to feel comfortable to think,
Oh, well, actually, I read a blog on what taboo is earlier, maybe I can give it a
go. Whereas if you didn't read that, maybe you wouldn't know and then you wouldn't
even you wouldn't feel confident enough to try it.
And finally, take inspiration from other webcam models.
And we've already mentioned that earlier as well, it's good to take inspiration from
each other and not like compared or, or anything like that, but to just take
inspiration and see like, Oh, I like this outfit that I can see that girl's wearing
or I like how she's wrote down a profile or I like this or, you know, I think maybe
I'll try that, but do it do it my way, you know.
And, but yes, I think that's it for the helpful tips and advice.
Does anybody have any tips or advice they want to add in themselves?
Would anyone like to share? No?
Okay. We've covered so much there, haven't we?
I mean, we've in that call. I mean, if anybody wants
to follow up anything, like we said, we've got there's so much more so many more
resources that we've got on the website, or through your mentor, or you know, there's
loads, loads more. So if there's anything you're not sure about, or you want some
more clarity on anything, let us know, we'd be happy to help you.
Yeah, and if anyone needs help with their profile with writing it, obviously, you
know, like the actual content of what to put in it or any ideas or anything like
that. And feel free to message me at any time, even if I'm not your mentor, just
anyone old or new, please just message me because I've spent a bit of time today
in trying to help with writing profiles. So if you need help, I'm here.
Thank you so much. Okay, ladies. Have
a lovely evening. I hope everyone who's going on cam has a great, a great night,
and loads of money. Yeah, thank you, ladies for coming along.
And this will be on the website. And if anyone wants to watch back, and yet we'll
see you on the next call. Hopefully, the next one is I'm just double checking now.
It's on Monday. It's on Monday. Yeah. Let me just check.
Monday. It's just the mental health check in.
So that's anyone that that needs it that wants to just come along and have a chat.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. I am UK time. Okay, then darlings.
I hope everyone has a nice evening. It's, it's half eight in the morning here in
Australia. So I think I'm going to go on cam.
Like I'm feeling like Yep, I'm ready to go on.
Like I feel good. So go and get myself ready.
And then and then yeah, I'm gonna go on now and take this good energy with me.
Yeah, do it. Good night, ladies. You ladies.
Yeah. Bye.